List quiz = [
  {
    "question":
        "What is the chemical formula for the common garnet species, almandine?",
    "options": [
      "Fe₃Al₂(SiO₄)₃",
      "Mg₃Al₂(SiO₄)₃",
      "Ca₃Al₂(SiO₄)₃",
      "Mn₃Al₂(SiO₄)₃"
    ],
    "answer": "Fe₃Al₂(SiO₄)₃"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which garnet species is known for its bright green color?",
    "options": [
      "Almandine",
      "Pyrope",
      "Tsavorite",
      "Spessartine"
    ],
    "answer": "Tsavorite"
  },
  {
    "question": "Garnet is most commonly found in which type of rock?",
    "options": [
       "Igneous",
       "Sedimentary",
       "Metamorphic",
       "Volcanic"
    ],
    "answer": "Metamorphic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Mohs hardness range of garnet?",
    "options": [
      "5.5 to 6.5",
      "6.5 to 7.5",
      "7.5 to 8.5",
      "8.5 to 9.5"
    ],
    "answer": "6.5 to 7.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which ancient civilization was garnet used as a talisman?",
    "options": [
       "Ancient Rome",
       "Ancient Egypt",
       "Ancient Greece",
       "Ancient China"
    ],
    "answer": "Ancient Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Garnet is the birthstone for which month?",
    "options": [
       "January",
       "February",
       "March",
       "April"],
    "answer": "March"
  },
  {
    "question": "What optical effect is seen in star garnets?",
    "options": [
       "Chatoyancy",
       "Asterism",
       "Adularescence",
       "Labradorescence"
    ],
    "answer": "Asterism"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which garnet species is often used as an abrasive material?",
    "options": [

      "Grossular",

      "Pyrope",
      "Almandine",

      "Uvarovite"
    ],
    "answer": "Almandine"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the specific gravity range for most garnet species?",
    "options": [
       "2.1 to 3.3",
       "3.1 to 4.3",
       "4.1 to 5.3",
       "5.1 to 6.3",],
    "answer": "3.1 to 4.3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country is a major producer of garnet gemstones?",
    "options": [
       "Brazil",
       "South Africa",
       "India",
       "Australia"
    ],
    "answer": "India"
  }
];
